CARINA DIAZ

Accomplished coordinator and administrator with experience in providing support to high-level operations and leadership for 8+ years. Helped with everything from facility representative, to data entry and preparing well-researched documents. Skilled at time-management, MS Office and seeking to balance my professional experience with my software development skills.

EDUCATION

UC DAVIS - Full Stack Web Development Certification

JUNE 2021 - PRESENT

- Front end and back end technology education.
- Browser Based Technologies and Databases
- Computer Science applied to JavaScript
- Server Side Development
- API Interaction

CSU STANISLAUS - Bachelors of Science, Health Science

JANUARY 2016 - JUNE 2019

- Focus on health care leadership and administration
- Work effectively within health care systems and/or organizations
- Employ evidence-based practice
- Apply quality improvement
- Implement and evaluate programs relating to health in a multicultural society

San Joaquin Delta College, CA - Associates of Science,

Mathematics and Science

JANUARY 2010 - MAY 2016

- Interdisciplinary studies of mathematics and science
- Focus on biology and chemistry

SKILLS

Computer Science, Browser Based Technologies and Databases

HTML/CSS, JavaScript/jQuery, Git, Responsive Design, Bootstrap, Handlebars, Local Storage, Session Storage, IndexedDB, React.js, MySQL, NoSQL, User Authentication, Progressive Web Applications (PWAs), MERN Stack (MongoDB,

Express.js, React.js, Node.js), API, JSON, AJAX, Algorithms (Searches, Sorts), Big O Notation, data Structures, Microsoft Office

Interdisciplinary Professional Skills

Office management & administration, Data entry, Scheduling & Time Management, Research skills, Problem solving, Detail oriented, Leadership, Communication, Project management, Process improvement, Purchasing, Inventory control, Customer service, Record keeping, Trainer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Health And Safety Coordinator — One Community Health

SEPTEMBER 2020 - SEPTEMBER 2021, SACRAMENTO

Managed Health and Safety programs for regulatory compliance and injury reduction. Gather and interpret data to identify and prevent issues before they cause major problems. Developed and coordinated departmental projects that contributed to equipment design changes. Business system modifications and revised employee work habits. As co-instructor for behavior-based safety process, trained & coached facility-wide staff employees and managers. Participated on the Executive Leadership Committees as well the Safety Committee lead that developed action plans for safety improvement and injury reduction. Hazard analysis, safety audits, and evaluated work job task requirements.

Compliance Coordinator — Cintas Corporation

JUNE 2017 - SEPTEMBER 2020, STOCKTON

Promoted to the role of Compliance Coordinator. Health and Safety Coordinator (HSC) duties, data management, maintenance coordinator, environmental and regulatory compliance administrator, accomplish organizational goals, manage critical staff, track and evaluate leading/lagging indicators, accident investigation, training coordinator and team lead. Assist HR with workers compensation reporting and representation tasks.

Maintenance Administrator — Cintas Corporation

DECEMBER 2014 - JUNE 2017, STOCKTON

Promoted to maintenance administrator. Supervisor assistant, database and document management. Scheduling staff and contractors, safety inspections, managed facility SharePoint site. Maintenance department health, safety, and regulatory compliance lead

Quality Assurance - Cintas Corporation

JANUARY 2010 - DECEMBER 2014, STOCKTON

Monitor quality of customer return products, maintain inventory, delivery scheduling, department safety and training coordination